Toho International Corporation Production
-Nice car, isn't it?
-Yeah!
Hey, that's MY car!
Th-thief!
Wait!! Ahhhhh!
Thank you. Hey, wait up!!
Produced by: Yutaka Fujioka, Shunji Oki
Planned by: Fujio Akazuka, Chika Nakayama
Original concept. Monkey Punch (Manga
Action Comics) Script. Hiroshi Nagano
Filmed by: Kenmuro Shigen Designer: Kazuo Takenaka Lighting:
Shoshichi Kojima Sound: Noboru Nishio Music: Masaru Satohn
Assistant Director: Koyu Shimura Coloring: Hakuto Taben Special effects: Jin Nakano
Editing: Sachiko Yamaji Still pictures: Koh Nakao Assistant Producer: Yo no ho Koh
Equipment:. Biken Promotions Sets: Toho Design Wardrobe: Kyoto Costuming Hair
and makeup: Katsura Kawaguchi Film developing: Toyo Developing Sound: Tokyo Eiga
Cast
Yuki Meguro
Hideko Ezaki, Shiro Itoh, Kunie Tanaka
Akira Hitomi, Takashi Ezaki,
Rinichi Yamamoto, Arihiro Fujimura
Maria Anzai, Megumi, Rena Natsuki, Poppies
Kiyoshi Maekawa, Akira Oizumi,
Eisei Amamoto, E. H. Eric
Sachio Sakai, Toki Shiozawa, Kokki Ishiyama,
Junichi Tanaka, Minoru Uezu, Sozo Fukuyama
Sanji Kojima, Katsuo Umino, Kyuji Aozora, Koji
Aozora Stunts: Uni Kizoh, Voice: Obei Toru
Kunie Tanaka
Directed by: Takashi Tsuboshima
Hey, you, take a look at this. Horrible, huh?
But I guess a fruitcake's
gotta forgive another fruitcake.
That's no way to act after appealing to a man's sex
drive. Now I'll have a hard time getting married.
You're gonna pay for this.
But my, you're a cutie!
Yuck.
Yuck? How rude.
H-hey, wait up!
Hey, you, don't go!
Just shut up.
Heyyy, wait up.
Arrrgh, that damn asshole. I'll get my revenge!
I got it.
Loooook, a beautiful naked woman is dead!
What?! Beautiful?! Naked?!
'Kaaaay, where is she?
She's very close by! Turn the corner
and it's the third building. Hurry!
I'll go on ahead of you.
No, I'll go ahead.
No, me. I was here first.
No, not so fast. I'M first.
Niiiiice.
Merci.
Hey, Sweetie!
Wanna go on a date with me tonight?
That was a very straightforward way to put it.
Of course it was. After all, I've been
waiting since the day I was born to meet you.
Do you know where I'm being taken right how?
I'm serious here.
I promise I'll go on a date with you
I wonder if you can.
Leave it to my psychokinesis.
I'll be expecting you tonight, then.
Bravo!
Seal it with a kiss!
What was that? My dream came true?
Awwww, come onnnn, someone help me!
I can't take it anymore.
Lupin the Third
Strange Psychokinetic Strategy
Security breach! Security breach!
Over there'll
Security breach!!
Ah, owww.
It's open.
Huh?
Aw man... it's open.
Dammit, where the hell did he run off to?
He he he. Idiots.
Come, Mademoiselle, you have nothing more
to fear. For at your side, you have a strong...
Who're you?
Huh, me? I'm Lupin.
Lunpen?
Not "Lunpen”, Lupin.
LUPIN. I get it.
Yup, exactly.
By the way, who are you?
Hmm, you rescued me without knowing?
Yup. It was love at first sight.
You have interesting taste.
Love comes at ya
unexpectedly sometimes. I guess.
Nevertheless, thank you.
You SHOULD thank me.
Otherwise I won't cooperate.
Goodnight, Lupin.
Gimme a break!
Listen,
if you underestimate me, you'll get in trouble.
Huh?
Don't let looks deceive you, I am the seventh Zenigata
descended from the famous Edo Hunter Heiji Zenigata.
I make even cranky kids shut up!
And don't forget, I'm on his staff, and I
descended from Echizen Ohka, making...
Not so fast. I descended from
Kinshiro Touyama, and I'm also...
Silence!I No one cares about you two!
Ouch! Son of a bitch.
Listen, where'd you put Mine Fujiko?
Where is she?
Where did she escape to?
We know you let her escape.
Mine Fujiko?
What a pretty name.
Moron.
Stop joking around, ya jackass.
Stop joking around.
Ouch!
Listen,
we know full well that you let Fujiko escape.
How do you know?
Isn't the fact that you're wearing
women's prison clothing enough?!
I think that's enough.
Sorry, but you're wrong.
I spent last night gazing up at
the starry sky as I went on a walk.
A walk?
Yup.
And then, my head was suddenly smacked,
stars came out of my eyes,
and when I came to, here I was.
Arrrgh, you jackass. You amuse me.
Very well. In that case,
I'll give you some extensive proof.
Listen, last night, many guards saw your face.
We're interrogating them on the
other side of the glass as we speak.
Ohhh.
He he he, how do you like that?
Scared?
No...
Are you scared now?
Owwiw I
Sir, I'm sorry to inform you that our withesses say the action
was too fast to catch the face of the criminal. That is all.
Whaaat?
Hmm?
He he he he. So sorry about that, Mr. Inspector.
This is getting to my head so
bad it's giving me a headache.
That's enough. Ow, my nose hurts!
L-Lupin, you say??
Qui.
By the way,
Do you know of the
phantom thief Arséne Lupin?
Of course! He was a brave man
of our mighty present-day France.
But... a poor, lost thief.
Amen.
Then do you know of his son, Arséne Lupin |17
No, not really.
Then I shall explain.
Lupin the 1st loved solitude. So while the first
Lupin was a sort of crafty artist who worked alone,
his son was a genius
at creating crime organizations.
Hmm, I see.
After he followed his father's footsteps, he united
the world's organized crime units in a heartbeat,
built 311 secret bases, and had
86,313 followers under the Lupin Empire.
Hmm, that's impressive!
Er, I mean, how frightening. Amen.
Amen.
Anyways, one day, Lupin the 2nd
was betrayed by his 86,313th recruit,
which caused the Lupin Empire
to be crushed by the Maccherone family.
Mm Mm mm,
Those Maccherone bastards!... How horrible.
Amen.
It's him. He's the sole living member
of the Lupin Empire, Daisuke Jigen.
Qui.
But... I wasn't the only survivor.
So, who else survived then?
The year was 1974!
But that's this year.
March 5th, at 8 AM!
Qui, oui.
In a small tea house
in Damascus, the capital of Syria.
I don't quite follow.
A certain organization ordered a certain bored and nearby man to
look at a certain magazine shoot, and made a certain discovery.
Certain, certain, what kind of certain?
Certainly here!
This is a shot of the magazine shoot he saw.
Hmm.
By magnifying this portion of the picture by 100.
Hmm, hmm.
And then another 100 times.
Ohhh.
And then, if you zoom in another 10 times.
Qui! Oui, oui, oui, OUI!
You know this man, don't you!
Hm mm mm mm.
It's a miracle. A miracle.
This boy is the one survivor of the massacre,
and the one true heir
to the Lupin Empire. He is Lupin the Third!
Look at his chest. The tattoo that Lupin the 2nd placed
on all of his children is all the proof you need.
My, I've never seen
something this fascinating before.
That is exactly why
I came to see you about this.
Yes, he was raised here in my orphanage.
Of course, we called him "Lupin”, but we
didn't realize he was really a Frenchman.
Probably because of his mother.
What do you mean?
His mother was Japanese.
In addition to being a
genius at creating organizations,
he was also a genius at creating children.
Oh, I see. I see.
Oh, I suddenly remember something.
This is everything about his life.
Lupin, age O.
Bad boy, Lupin!
Lupin, age 3.
Lupin, age 5.
Bad boy, Lupin!
Lupin, age 10.
Lupin, age 15.
Bad boy, Lupin!
I can still hear it, the sound of my voice.
Teaching Lupin of the harshness of life.
I was hoping he would return
to us a shining star of Japan,
but ever since then, he's been missing.
Wow, thanks for all the stories.
Merci, Mum Pére Monkey face.
Non, Mokkinpart!
Oh, adieu, Mum Pére Mokkinpart.
Don't move.
Hey now, you should knock.
At last I found you, Daisuke Jigen.
Did the Mob send you?
Suppose so.
What a convenient circumstance. Right
after I kill you, a priest can pray for you.
No, he can pray for YOU.
Shitl... Adieu.
0.8 seconds.
Oops, I drew blood again.
Pray for these bastards.
Amen.
Hmm?
New autumn fashion.
Excuse me.
That face?...
My wallet!
Freeze.
Stick 'em up.
If you think I'm gonna
give it back, you're wrong.
Sorry, but I'm not that cheap a guy.
I stopped you because I think
you're the one I've been looking for.
Look at me.
Like this?
Hmph. You're pretty good.
Whaddaya think?
How many guns do you have??
Hmm?
Ah, I give up.
Pardon me, Monsieur.
But are you by any
chance Arséne Lupin the Third?
Exactly. That's correct.
To think this man is Lupin the Third. Jackass.
What?! How dare you use
that language in my presence!
No, I didn't mean you,
I was talking about Lupin.
No doubt, he is Arséne Lupin. It's in this file.
I see, hmm, oh, oui, oui, wonderful.
I see, I see.
-Can you read that? -Not at all.
Moron! You read it like this.
"Pseudo French"
QOui, Madame.
I'm not a Madame!
Monsieur.
Inspector Zenigata.
Yes?
I order you here and now to
investigate Arséne Lupin the Third.
I will arrest him immediately!
No, I didn't ask you to arrest him, not
unless we find reasonable evidence to do so.
I vow I will arrest him!
Fine, do whatever you want! You imbecile.
Got it?!
We understand, Sir!
Promise me you will capture Lupin!
If you fail, you will both be...
Come, what are you farting around for?
Look for him! Now's no time to eat!
Sheesh, what laziness I have to put up with.
We found him!
That was too quick! So, where is he?
This way!
Where abouts?
Ummm, around here.
How horrible.
To think that the heir to the Lupin Empire...
Is living in such filth.
Ahhh, how pathetic.
It's not like this's the only place I live.
But please explain to me, Master.
Hey, I'd cut the Master-crap if I were you.
We're equals now.
Go ahead and call me Lupin.
In that case, Lupin, why are you living like this?
I think of Tokyo, no...
I think of all of Japan,
for that matter, as my property.
What?
So some days I feel like
staying in first class hotels or condos,
but other days
I feel like sleeping under the stars.
Oh, I suppose that is nice.
Guess ya don't believe me.
Fine, then we'll go to a nicer place.
Where?
The Residence Hall.
Residence Hall?
Yeah. It's a place that was
built from a hefty sum of money.
Mr. Ponpydo can't make his reservation, and no one's going
to take his place, so I figured we'd go check it out.
Are you awake?
Arrrrgh,
looks like the rats have come out of hiding.
Sakuradamon's rats, that is.
Poor thing, he's had a lot of brain trauma.
Swarm!!
Lupin, run for it! I'll handle things here!
I have business with Lupin.
Dammit, what do you mean business?
You're in the way.
No, YOU'RE in the way.
No, YOU are.
Dammit, just who do you think I am?!
Wait up!
That way! That way!
This way! This way!
I am Lupin's sole subordinate, Daisuke Jigen.
Out of my way.
Move it.
Get lost.
You heard 'em.
Right...
There he isl!
Get him!!
Shit!
This is the first time the Law has ignored me.
Damn arrogant jerks.
This way.
Hey, this way!
Ah, what're you doing there? Why am I on top?
Let's go.
Ah, Inspector, wait!
-Here, have a shoe. -Thank you.
You look splendid.
Now's no time
to be doing this, Lupin's getting away.
Let's go! Good.
Over there!
Hello, boys.
Damn it! Full speed ahead...
And break suddenly at the right curve!
Ouuuch.
It's overheated.
We don't have time for that.
Damn, Lupin is getting away.
Have a nice trip.
Ohhh, here he is.
Stop!
Hey, don't you understand what "stop" means?!
Hey, come this way, dammit! How frustrating!!
Up yours!
How dare you speak to me that way, Lupin!
Mmmm, I'll try my psychokinesis on you.
Ahhh! I can't swim! Help me, Lupin!
That Lupin,
I wonder where he disappeared off to?
Yo. Took ya long enough, Jigen.
Oh, is that you, Lupin?
Can you tell me what's going on?
What?
You know what?
This room was borrowed and set aside for you.
Yeah, and that's why I'm here.
But no one told you, so how did you know?
Because I'm Lupin.
Yeah, I get it.
Hey, what happened to the furniture?
What furniture?
Don't play innocent. There was a
bed, chairs, table, TV and a refrigerator.
Oh,
those were in the way, so I gave them away.
Gave them away?? Who'd you give them to?
An outstanding Japanese citizen.
I thought this would...
Be uncomfortable for me.
What the hell is this?!
This isn't funny.
Under that bed, I hid a 30 billion
yen deposit note from a Swiss bank.
It's the net fortune of the Lupin Empire.
Means nothing to me.
Means nothing??
Son, do you have any idea what I went
through for you? What sweat and tears I...
I suppose I was wrong about you.
Your father and grandfather must
be turning in their graves right now.
I guess this shatters any chance
of the Lupin Empire's restoration.
I think a Democracy is
better than an Empire, personally.
Lupin...
Lupin.
Aw, stop it.
Hm, ahhh! That's Lupin!
What is it?
You could've just used the stairs,
Sir. You're pretty spry, huh?
Poor guy.
What're you looking at?
Oh, just observing the goings on of our world.
Say, Jigen, being alive sure is fun, isn't it?
We eat when we're
hungry, sleep when we're sleepy.
And fall in love when we want to
fall in love. What else do ya need?
Yes, but Son.
Yahoo!
Lupin!
Hi.
No matter when I see you,
you always have a strange look.
If it bothers you, I'll become normal.
Amen.
God is the Lord of normality.
I'll agree to that.
Fujiko.
I want diamonds.
As you wish.
I also want emeralds.
I also want opals and sapphires and rubies.
As you wish. As you wish. As you wish.
Take it easy!
Here's directions to the Trade Department.
Trade Department?
They're trading jewels
from all over the world there.
By today's value,
you should get 560 billion yen.
560 billion?!
And you want me to get that for you?
Will you?
Lupin takes orders from no one.
But...
He does take requests sometimes.
Come on, pleeeease?
Okay, I accept. But before that.
Fine, I get it.
Ummm. An eye for an eye.
Lupin never falls for the same
trick twice. Now, this time for sure!
Yahoo!
Get the job done tonight. Got it?
Hey, that's no way to treat me.
H-hey.
Dammit.
How the hell'm I supposed to get home?
He's coming, he's coming. Close to Sherlock
Holmes's tail, a second runner has approached.
Which contender is he? The thing shining on his chest
appears to be an "L", and he is running at an amazing speed.
The space between him and
Holmes is a mere 10 meters.
"I pursues, Holmes retreats. "L
still pursues, well, what's happened?
Are they even? They're even! Holmes,
hang in there! Oh, "L" has passed him!
"L" has won. "L" has just
broken through the white tape.
I-it's Lupin.
Hey, look at that, hey,
Can't you answer me?
Hey, look at that.
Are you asleep? Hey, wake up!!
Mmm, you jackass!!
Yes, yes? Phone for you, Sir.
Shut up!
But it's a young woman.
Idiot! Why didn't you say so? What a waste.
Hello. Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hello?
Yes, yes, this is Zenigata.
What? You're Mine Fujiko?
All's well.
All's well here, too.
How are you going to get in? There
are guards on the inside and outside.
Lupin's dictionary
doesn't have "impossible" in it.
What a carefree spirit. But could
you please let me down already?
I can't get enough of this excitement.
Mm Mm mm, you idiot.
Ah, oops.
Lupin, are you okay? Lupin!!
Oh, that's nothing.
Come on.
Hey, gimme a light.
Okay, okay.
That's not enough, gimme a LIGHT.
Owww.
Go away over there.
No.
Don't talk back, go away.
Welcome here.
Who's that? Looks young.
It's a woman.
Yes, a woman.
I'm going.
No, we should match for it.
Rock, paper, scissors, match! Since I
lost, I'm going. Shall I hold it for you?
Woof, woof, meowww.
What is it?
We're a special patrol unit.
Um, what exactly is your business here?
I'll show you.
Splendid.
What is it?
The emergency bell.
It doesn't look like anything is amiss.
Anyway, let's check it out.
'Sirl
Hey, look.
What's that?
Goodnight.
Yeah. Ohhh, pachinko!
Jigen should be here any minute. Come, hurry.
Nnngh, I can't move. Stupid!
Here it comes.
Lupin!
Okay.
Hurry.
Right on schedule. Let's go.
There's still more.
What?
There's a large safe behind that clock.
A safe?
Yes.
The real expensive stuff is in there.
Women sure are greedy creatures.
Can't you open it?
Don't patronize me.
My dictionary doesn't have a word for...
A word for "impossible,"
right? Pleeeeease, open it?
Guess I have to.
Good boy.
Wow, you've opened it.
It was nothing.
Lupin's psychokinetic powers are king.
It's Lupin! Get him!!
He's over there. Grab him!
What're you trying to do?
Ah, that way!
Stupid, stupid, stupid! How dare
they leave me behind! Dammit!! Police!!
It's Lupin. Ah, he's over there!
Pull on it! Umph.
Pull on it, Go!
What the hell?
Goll
Catch him...
Owww.
Don't imitate me.
Arrrgh, what're you guys doing?
Hang in there!
Adieu.
Arrrgh, I've got a headache.
Hurry up, he's coming!
Inspector Zenigata, spank, spank.
Shit! How dare he patronize me.
I'll get him yet.
Increase speed!
My! Inspector.
I am a bachelor. Ahhh, ack!
The wheel.. the wheel...
Hey, pull yourself together.
When you turn, you'll crash!!!
See?
Lupin got away AGAIN...
Umph.
Hmm, I don't know whose car that was.
What's the number?
I didn't have time to memorize that.
Lupin Potato,
third-rate, klutz, lazy-ass, yo' mamal!
Damn!
Come sniff it out.
Smell, smell, and smell some more.
What are we smelling for?
Isn't it obvious?
The least smelly car is the fishiest!
Ohhh, smart.
What're you standing around for? Gol!
Idiots. Stop standing still like pieces of shit.
Those guys really ARE stupid.
Elusive Thief Lupin has arrived in Japan.
Lupin the Third was still alive!!
Naturally so. He sneaked out of the jewel shop.
Zenigata and his officers are presently in
hot pursuit of the one who stole the jewels,
but they have no leads as of now and it looks like
the investigation will take longer than anticipated.
Say, Lupin, since they can't find the jewels,
does that mean
someone else got them before we did?...
Hey, are you listening to me?
Yeahhh, I'm listening.
Hey, Lupin.
The only person that makes
sense from all of this is Fujiko.
She must have betrayed us.
No! My Fujiko is not that kind of woman!
Idiot!
You're just blinded by your love for her.
No! My Fujiko is not that kind of woman!
What's with the
"Fujiko, Fujiko?" I'm Yamako Asama!
Mount Asama
Buon giorho, Buon giorno. Good morning.
Good morning, brothers of the Black Streets.
I'm sure you're already aware of this, but a
very powerful enemy of ours, the Lupin Empire,
still has a living blood-heir who has returned to
Japan. His name is apparently "Lupin the Third".
He is a young man with all the skills and intellect
of his grandfather, and if we leave him alone,
he will someday grow to be a threat to us.
So my order to you is to kill
his sole follower, Daisuke Jigen.
That is the best way to eliminate the
Lupin Empire from the face of the Earth.
If any of you are captured or killed in the
process, our organization will hot compensate.
Keep that in mind.
I pray for your success.
This tape will now self-destruct.
Hurry!
Huh?
Oh, that way.
Oh, it's an eruption!
Where's the tape?
Since the tape is useless,
you need to find another way.
Oops.
Ahh, who're you?
What're you doing!
My wallet and one kiss isn't enough.
You saying I stole your wallet?
I already got it back.
And this too. It was easier than I thought.
Pervert!
If that's what you want,
I can be even more perverse.
Give it back!
Ahhh, that felt good.
Huh? I feel unusually calm.
Ah,
she got me.
Ah, what a fix I'm in.
Who're you?
An assassin.
You startled me. Who sent you?
I can't say.
Is that the Assassin's Code?
Shut up.
Come on.
What?
You don't get what just happened?
Let's review it in slow motion.
You still didn't take it out.
Idiot.
I got rid of 'em, I got rid of 'em, I got rid of 'em.
That's how it is.
What the hell is this?
Oh, Lupin, you must stop doing that.
Ah, stop it. No, you mustn't.
Oh, oh dear, mmmmm,
Please, Lupin, don't come any closer.
What the hell's happening? Well, whatever.
Hey, Lupin.
Oh not
What the hell is that?
Lupin...
In accordance with
Criminal Law, article 175...CUT!
Stop fooling around.
Lupin...
For the same reason... CUT!
He he he, again!
Got it.
Oh, so he's come out. Goood.
Wait.
Oh my, something's come flying. Oops,
he he he, you suck.
Hmm?
Why you...
you jerk.
Dammit!!
Hmm mm...
All these nuns are too pretty.
Hi!
Whaaat?
Let's go!
It's up to the man
To take his chance at love.
Da-da-da-da-dal
Bitter cigarettes bring on the mood.
Passionate words bring on the mood.
You're a woman's man. You're a woman's man.
We want you to
roughly take charge of our hearts...
Please do it again!
Damn pussy-cats! Comel!
Smooch.
Tickle, tickle.
Eeeecew! Noooo!
What the, what the? What the hell's going on?
A guy was found at the wharf
last night with a blow to his head.
And the two who dropped in the woods by the
mansion. Both of these look like Lupin's doing.
I KNOW he did it!
Yes, but Sir,
We don't really have any proof Lupin did it.
If nothing else, we know he did it.
Sirl
We found another one by the bay!
It's Lupin! It's gotta be Lupin!
Yes, but Sir.
Sirl
There's just been an earthquake in 1zu!
It was Lupin! It must've been Lupin's doing!
Sirl
Our Mike just gave birth to five Kittens!
That must also be Lupin's doing!
Thought so.
Sirll
Lupin has just turned himself in!
It's Lupin! That damn Lupin did... WHAT?!!
Yo.
LUPIN!
Ahhh, what a drag.
The world's been so crazy these days,
I wanted to go to a quiet place to get some
peace, and your cell block looked quite appealing,
so I decided to stay here.
Oh.
Will you show me to my room?
Ummm, did we have one available?
Don't we have one on the far wing open?
Ah, yes, we do.
Well, come with us, Sir.
Step this way, dear patron.
Dinner will be served at seven o'clock, Sir.
Hey, wait up!
Yes, yes,
Did you call, Sir?
Oh, he's gone.
Stupid.
Lupin the Third has been arrested!!
Lupin turned himself in!
Inspector Zenigata gives him a special room.
Buon giorno. Good morning,
followers of the Dark Streets.
As you well know, our arch enemy,
Lupin the Third has been arrested,
and it is apparent that he will be executed soon.
Since this mission has become meaningless,
be it Miami, Nice, Acapulco, or Southeast
Asia, you can all take leave wherever you wish.
If you want to disobey me.
Now, brothers, I would like to draw
your attention to the picture on the wall.
This is an example of the pottery that was produced
at the end of the Jomon Era in northeastern Japan.
It is called a "darkened clay figure."
It is also said that these darkened clay figures
were replicas of aliens who landed in the area.
How ridiculous.
Don't laugh, you fools.
The proof lies in the several clay figures that
were discovered disappearing in strange ways.
Also, in the eyes of the most
recently discovered clay figure,
It was discovered that there were multi-colored jewels
made of an unknown substance embedded in the eye sockets.
What's more, the picture can only show
one color, and what's even more intriguing...
...is the fact that the jewels are thought to contain
psychokinetic energy we humans have yet to harness.
All the wealthy superstitious people of the
world are scrambling to get a piece of it.
And this brings me to your task. I want you to steal
this clay figure, and sell it to the highest bidder.
I call it "Operation Psychokinesis". If any of you are killed or captured
during the mission, the organization will not compensate, so be aware.
Well, I pray for your success.
This tape will self-destruct in...
Just kidding, no explosion.
However, it WILL make a noise.
I certainly can't let THIS get away.
Good thing it was just a noise. Ha ha ha.
Who's there?
Damn.
Wait.
Wait!!
Ah, that way!
Get her quick!
Wait!
Get her!
Stop!!
Nice try, boys.
I don't like this.
Let me out. Hey, let me out, please?
Hey, let me out. You'll be sorry!
How much longer do
you plan on staying locked up in here?
Well, Lupin?
Dunno.
The food stinks here, but it's very relaxing.
Stop joking around!
Son, what are you going to do
about rebuilding the Lupin Empire?
Didn't I tell ya? I don't plan on rebuilding it.
Ah, I see.
Fine, do as you wish.
Poor thing. To think your life with Fujiko is over.
What?! Hey, what'd you just say?!
I didn't say anything.
Jigen-san, your hat and beard
are so sexy. Please continue.
According from a reliable source.
Listen, from a reliable source.
Your Fujiko has been captured
by the Maccherone Organization.
Whaaaat?!
Good job guarding him.
He he he, oh, our pleasure.
Hmm? Hey.
Yeah?
A lawyer just left here, right?
Yeah, he did.
-And then, another lawyer also
just left, right? -Yeah he did.
And then, looking in here, I see Lupin is gone.
Looks like it.
You let Lupin get away?!
You idiots!
I'll kill you!
-I'll kill you, I'll kill you,
I'll kill you! -Help! Help! Help!
Come back!
Where'd he go? Let's get him.
Stinky.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
You idiots!
Sir, that hurt, that hurt!
-Mr. Zenigata! -General!
Ahhh, it's no use.
Stop playing around! Come here!
This capsule is capable of tolerance to large explosions
and shocks, making the clay figure inside indestructible.
Good job.
Excuse me.
So then, Inspector Zenigata.
Yes! I cannot apologize enough.
I, Zenigata, in penance for my sins,
am willing to shatter my bones to...
What the hell are you talking about?
Er, yes, what I mean is that
you may punish me as you wish.
Silence! I'm giving you orders for Operation P!
Huh? Operation P?
What's that, Sir?
It's a mission to move this, the clay figure with psychokinetic
powers, to the nation's top science facility for protection.
It's called "Operation P" for short. That is all.
I see. So you were
appointed the leader of that mission.
Of course.
I knew it.
Well, congratulations!
Thank you.
Future General Superintendent!
Don't go that far.
-Official announcement. -Here it comes.
Suddenly cancel led.
I'm speaking from Point A,
Point A. Our target has just left.
Brothers.
let's go.
Okay.
Hey, who the hell are you?
Hi. Do you know where my Fujiko-chan is?
What? Oh?
Dammit!!
Fujiko-chan.
Umph.
Bastard.
I'm sorry.
What about?
Oops, I don't have time to play.
Hey, who the hell are you?
Bastard.
Ah, how nostalgic, Fujiko's smell.
Hey! Where did you put Fujiko?
Where did you put my girlfriend?
Lupin...
Are you crazy? There is a very
expensive national treasure in there.
To me, Fujiko is the ultimate national treasure.
Sheesh, here he goes again.
Let's get going.
Okay.
Uh-oh, a mysterious helicopter.
It must be that jackass, Lupin.
Heyyyy, what is it? Move the boulder.
Ohhhh, Sir.
Have we begun to revamp our waterways?
Or is Japan beginning to sink?
Stop talking rubbish and move the boulder.
'Sirt Go!
Go!
Umph.
We're on it.
We're doing very well.
Umph.
Gimme a fist.
Good job!
Idiots!
What?
Ultra powerful Offensive Organization speaking.
Officers, resistance is futile. Hand
yourselves over in peace, or we will kill you all.
What?! Get him!!
Get him!!
Don't throw away your life like that, Zenigata.
Dammit. You think you can just steal the show?
Does he know him?
Lupin, help me!
Leave it to me.
I'll get'cha out of there right away.
Shoot!
What the hell? An earthquake?
Hey, ah, there he is! Bastard!
Lupin, hang in there.
Dammit, you asshole!
This should do it.
Lupin!
Save the love scene for later. Let's go.
Ahhhh, the sea, the sea.
Save the love scene for later, remember?
What the hell is that?
Dammit, stupid mobsters. I'll
never give them the capsule.
What's that?
What?
Hey, you can't take that!
Stop, thief! Shoot him!
Shoot him!
Not even close.
Charge now!!
Huh? What?
I said, we're charging now. Go!
Yeah, yeah. Charge.
Okaaaay. Banzail!
We did it! Haha! Kiss my ass.
Check this out.
Wowww, I'm impressed!
This should work.
We'll escape through that window.
Hey, wait a minute. Before that, Fujiko.
Weren't we saving that for later?
There might not be a later.
What was that noise?
Ignore it, ignore it.
Fujiko.
Lupin
Heyyy, where're you going? Stop playing.
It is a bit strange. I wonder what's going on.
Hurry.
Listen, I think something's not right.
Nooo, just ignore it. No matter what happens,
I'd gladly go to the bottom layer of Hell for you.
Hang in there.
Hurry, hurry, grab on!
Oh, that hurt.
We can make it.
It must be falling off the cliff.
Yeah. Let's go while we can.
Ahhh, help melt!
You sure take your pants off a lot.
Idiot! It's not like I want to take them off.
Ah! I can't go on.
Ahhh, help meee.
Help!
Lupin, hang in there.
Heeeey, Jigen.
Do something, will ya?
Lupin, I love you. I love you.
Ahhh, I wish you would've told me that sooner.
Dammit.
Oh no, I wonder if the
gasoline tank was just punctured.
Ah, we're saved. Lupin!
Am I dreaming?
No.
But I wonder where we are?
I thank you, Arséne Lupin the Third.
Weren't you going to give that to me?
Of course not. If it weren't for Lupin and Jigen,
the national treasure would have been taken overseas.
I'm very sorry, Sir. But seeing as how
Lupin is a major criminal, I thought...
There is no evidence of that!
Yes, but he has killed countless men.
Your proof? If he did, it was in self-defense.
He tried to steal expensive jewels!
You have no solid evidence!
I have withesses.
Who?
Me.
You're not trustworthy.
After all, you let the mob bosses escape.
Yes, I wouldn't have,
but Lupin used unfair tactics to...
Nevertheless, the only evidence I have is that
Lupin the Third protected our national treasure.
Your next mission is to locate him and give
him this official thank you. Understand?!
Yeah.
-Don't "Yeah" me!
-Yes, sirrrrr. -Too long! -Yes, sir!
At the rate things are going, I
don't see a Lupin Empire at all.
More like a Lupin retirement home.
Shut up.
Lupin!
At last I have found you. Owww!
Ah, here he comes again.
Ah! Lupin!
Lupin, don't go!
Stop playing around!
Don't you want your official thank you?
I'll arrest you otherwise!
I'm telling you to stop!!
Ahhh, I've run quite a ways. I'm tired.
There he is!
Ah! There he is! Gol
Lupin, wait!
I'll just throw this away!
Lupin, wait!!!
THE END